A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Chancellor of the Virginia Community College System, 1964-2012
Library of Virginia
- Series VIII: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 51054], 1971-2007., Extent: 24 cu. ft. (24 boxes). (Box 1-24)
  - Special Audit, Maintenance Reserve Fund, 1990-1992 (Box 1)
  - Proposal for designation of Emporia as Southside Virginia Community College Campus Location, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Task Force Rport on Colleges, Campuses and Facilites, 1990 (Box 1)
  - JLARC Review of the Virginia Community College System, 1990 (Box 1)
  - VCCS Regional meeting, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Academic and Student Affairs, 2006 (Box 2)
  - ACCT, 2006 (Box 2)
  - ACOP, 2006 (Box 2)
  - ACOP Committee assignments, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Achieving the Dream, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Accounts, Dept. of, 2006 (Box 2)
  - AS & R Data regarding graudation rates, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Academic Services and Research, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Academic calendar year, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Administrative and Executive Assistant Professional Development, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Awards, Bellweather, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Authorized signatures, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Articulation Agreement, Excelsior College, 2006 (Box 2)
  - American Council on Education, Spellings Commission report, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Association of Community Colleges, 2006 (Box 2)
  - AIS Implementation Workgroup, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Emergency Management, Dept. of, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Enrollment, 2006 (Box 2)
  - e-Plan, Revised, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Foundation for Virginia, 2006 (Box 2)
  - FRS year end report, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Full time faculty issue, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Facilities Management Services, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Federal Resources Consultant, 2006 (Box 2)
  - FOIA, 2006 (Box 2)
  - General Assembly, 2006 (Box 2)
  - , 2006 (Box 2)
  - , 2006 (Box 3)